Rogelio Schevenin Jr

Computer Science Undergraduate

Self-motivated HSF Scholar and student with mid level of experience working on multiple projects. Published on the App Store and have built website portfolios for myself, for friends, family, and clients. Passionate and hardworking with penchant for meeting deadlines. Interested in role with company promoting best practices and offering diverse customer projects with a primary focus in providing a real world impact through an internship or job as a Software Engineer.

Work History

2016-02 -Current

Web Developer

PHS Boys Soccer Booster Club, Woodland, CA

- Developed and currently maintain e-commerce site to maximize company revenue and support ~500 unique monthly visitors.
- Determined coding requirements for site creation, including e-commerce capability and specialized scripts via PayPal integration.
- Strengthened company brand and identity by creating distinctive website and logo.

2019-06 -2019-08

Activity Leader II

City Of Woodland, Woodland, CA

- Ensured group of 60 kids participating in city Youth Summer Camp (STFC) were safe and enjoyed summer.
- Responsible for working with team of like-minded leaders to plan activities, leading youth through activities, and keeping parents updated with following week's activity schedule.
- Occasionally responsible for communicating with kids and their parents to resolve issues.
- Fostered environment where youth were able to developed personal relationships.
- Maintained excellent attendance record, with 100% attendance rate.

Contact

Address

2501 Ortiz Avenue Woodland, CA, 95776

Phone

530-383-1476

E-mail

rogelio@schevenin.com

Skills

Software Development (Java, Python, Swift)



Development standards



HTML and CSS proficiency



Algorithms and data structures



Troubleshooting



2018-07 - Sales Associate

Davis Legacy Soccer League, Davis, CA

- Worked with other Sales Associates to collaboratively reach targets, consistently meeting or exceeding personal quotas.
- Increased revenue by selling tickets to over 5000 customers.

2018-06 - Activity Leader I

City Of Woodland, Woodland, CA

- Ensured kids participating in city Youth Summer
 Camp (STFC) had safe and enjoyable summer.
- Responsible for working with team of like-minded leaders to plan activities and lead youth through activities.
- Maintained excellent attendance record, with 100% attendance rate.

Education

2019-08 -Current

2019-08

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

San Diego State University - San Diego, CA

- Member of Weber Honors College
- Minor in Interdisciplinary Studies
- Coursework in Algorithm Design and Data Structures
- 3.54/4.00 GPA